



OBJECTIVE

I have over 3 years of content marketing experience working and 1 year of experience in Digital Marketing, I hope I will use my abilities and skills in the best way of achieving the organization's goals. Work in a professional and self-motivated. dynamic. creative environment. and with cooperative counterparts. Have the opportunity to learn more knowledge and skill.

EXPERIENCE

CONTENT SPECIALIST

MOBILE WORLD GROUP (DIEN MAY XANH)

(AUGUST 2019 - MARCH 2020)

- Planning / Manage / Create / Edit web content and provide relevant support with SEO. Website.
- Guides and supervisors to ensure the progress and quality of content and images from the freelancer and the internship.
- Connected to IT team to optimize image, content to improve user experience on the website.
- Assist procurement team to find business opportunities for new categories.
- Worked with media team to plan and produce product introduction videos.
- Measure, report performance of all digital marketing campaigns & KPIs.
- Training Product.

CONTENT TEAM LEADER

GOHA DIGITAL MARKETING

(SEPTEMBER 2016 - JANUARY 2019)

- Develop targeting strategies that will improve marketing and merchandising performance.
- Planning & implementing construction, developing content for website systems and social channels.
- Creating advertising content and content types such as: Landing page, Facebook posts, website news articles, messenger, email, Press Release ...
- Work closely with assistant editors and freelancer execute the content strategy to increase brand awareness, website traffic, search engine rank, and lead generation activities.
- Ensure projects follow to budget and time.
- Build and training team.

CONTENTWRITER

KIVI COSMETICS

(JUNE 2015 - SEPTEMBER 2016)

- Develop targeting strategies that will improve marketing and merchandising performance.
- Create / Edit web content and provide relevant support with SEO, Website, Landing page, Sale Page.
- Report per day to line manager.

SKILLS

- Demonstrated ability to perform detailed work with high level of accuracy and attention to detail.
- Writing ability (e.g. SEO, SEM, Landing page, Newsletters, Newspapers...).
- Understanding of the communication channels content and approaches.
- Strong computer skills and design skills including proficiency with Microsoft Office, Photoshop, Premiere, Adobe Illustrator...
- Good communication, analytical and problem solving skills.

OTHER SKILLS

- Can learn quickly, responsible, ability to work under high pressures, careful.
- Hard-wordking, self-motivated, patient.
- Willing to learn and adapt fast.
- Deal with orders and issues from sales teams and distributors.
- Supervise the distribution system and take action immediately for any out-of stock problems.
- Build and maintain relationships with colleagues as well as with suppliers and agencies.

EDUCATION

University (2011-2015):

- University of Social Sciences and Humanities.

Training course (2017):

- Design For Marketing - RIO Class.

Training course (2018):

- Copywriter at Vietnam Marcom.